Guide to Philosophy Talk SC1118
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional program audio, Accession ARCH-2015-121
  - Walter Sinnott-Armstrong, Moral dilemmas and moral ambiguity, 2006 Dec 24; 2015_121_b2_36; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - David Thomson, Philosophy and film, 2006 Dec 17; 2015_121_b2_37; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Patricia Churchland, Philosophy and neuroscience, 2006 Dec 10; 2015_121_b2_38; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - John McDermott, American pragmatism, 2006 Dec 3; 2015_121_b2_39; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Martha Nussbaum, The indispensable emotions, 2006 Nov 26; 2015_121_b2_40; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Tamar Schapiro, What is a child?, 2006 Nov 19; 2015_121_b2_41; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Dreaming, 2006 Nov 12; 2015_121_b2_42; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Kathleen Sullivan, Separation of powers, 2006 Nov 8; 2015_121_b2_43; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Philip Clayton, Believing in God, 2006 Oct 29; 2015_121_b2_44; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Lera Boroditsky, Language and thought, 2006 Oct 22; 2015_121_b2_45; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Jenann Ismael, The strange world of quantum reality, 2006 Oct 15; 2015_121_b2_46; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Denis Philips, Karl Popper, 2006 Oct 8; 2015_121_b2_47; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Paul Franks, Jewish philosophy, 2006 Oct 1; 2015_121_b2_48; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Charles Griswold, Forgiveness, 2006 Sep 26; 2015_121_b2_49; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Irv Yalom, Schopenhauer, 2006 Sep 19; 2015_121_b2_50; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Peter Singer, Global poverty, 2006 Sep 12; 2015_121_b2_51; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Stephen Holmes, Liberty vs. security, 2006 Sep 5; 2015_121_b2_52; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Philosophy Talk's 100th episode, 2006 Aug 29; 2015_121_b2_53; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Dan Sperber, Pragmatics: language in action, 2006 Aug 22; 2015_121_b2_54; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Hans Gumbrecht, Athletic beauty, 2006 Aug 15; 2015_121_b2_55; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Elizabeth Kiss, Race, class, and inequality, 2006 Aug 8; 2015_121_b2_56; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Liz Haman, Brian Weatherson, and Sean Kelly, The future of philosophy, 2006 Aug 1; 2015_121_b2_57; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - John Cooper, Stoicism, 2006 Jul 25; 2015_121_b2_58; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Leda Cosmides, The evolution of the human mind, 2006 Jul 11; 2015_121_b2_59; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Deborah Rhode, Leadership, 2006 Jun 27; 2015_121_b2_60; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Debra Satz, Prostitution, 2006 Jun 20; 2015_121_b2_61; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Robert Scharf, Zen, 2006 Jun 13; 2015_121_b2_62; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Allen Wood, Hegel, 2006 Jun 6; 2015_121_b2_63; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Alison Gopnik, The nature of imagination, 2006 May 30; 2015_121_b2_64; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - John Fischer, Is free will an illusion?, 2006 May 23; 2015_121_b2_65; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Ashley Wallingford, Summer reading, 2006 May 16; 2015_121_b2_66; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Sam Barondes, Neurocosmetology, 2006 May 2; 2015_121_b2_67; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Alexander Nehamas, What is Art?, 2006 Apr 25; 2015_121_b2_68; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Robert Audi, Religion and the secular state, 2006 Apr 18; 2015_121_b2_69; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Jul es Coleman, Philosophy and the law, 2006 Apr 11; 2015_121_b2_70; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Chris Bobonich, Aristotle, 2006 Apr 4; 2015_121_b2_71; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Michael Cholbi, Suicide, 2006 Mar21; 2015_121_b2_72; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Gideon Rosen, What is number, 2006 Mar14; 2015_121_b2_73; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Lanier Anderson, Existentialism, 2006 Mar7; 2015_121_b2_74; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Tony Veale, The science of humor, 2006 Feb 28; 2015_121_b2_75; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Helen Fisher, Marriage and monogamy, 2006 Feb 14; 2015_121_b2_76; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Lucius Outlaw, W. E. B. DuBois, 2006 Feb 7; 2015_121_b2_77; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Anna Eshoo, Legislating values, 2006 Jan 31; 2015_121_b2_78; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Peter Godfrey-Smith, Philosophy of science, 2006 Jan 24; 2015_121_b2_79; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Daniel Dennett, Intelligent design, 2006 Jan 17; 2015_121_b2_80; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - John Searle, Mystery of mind, 2006 Jan 10; 2015_121_b2_82; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Terry Tamminen, Progress and the environment, 2006 Jan 3; 2015_121_b2_82; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Alexander Nehamas, What is beauty?, 2005 Dec 27; 2015_121_b2_83; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Peter Gilgen, Kant, 2005 Dec 13; 2015_121_b2_84; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Geoffrey Stone, Freedom of speech in times of war, 2005 Dec 6; 2015_121_b2_85; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Martha Nussbaum, Friendship, 2005 Nov 29; 2015_121_b2_86; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Anne Fausto-Sterling, Gender, 2005 Nov 15; 2015_121_b2_87; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Josh Ober, Is this any way to run a democracy?, 2005 Nov 8; 2015_121_b2_88; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - David Hilbert, Berkeley, 2005 Nov 1; 2015_121_b2_89; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Steven Meyer, Art and the suspension of disbelief, 2005 Oct 18; 2015_121_b2_90; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Daniel Herwitz, Reconciliation, 2005 Oct 11; 2015_121_b2_91; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Christopher lehrich, The occult philosophy, 2010 Oct 31; 2015_121_b2_92; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Carrie Menkel-Meadow, Bargaining with the Devil, 2010 Oct 24; 2015_121_b2_93; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Jack Bowen, Philosophy for the young: corrupting or empowering?, 2010 Nov 5; 2015_121_b2_94; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Neil van Leeuwen, Self-Dec eption, 2010 Aug 29; 2015_121_b2_95; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Jenann Ismael, The strange world of quantum reality, 2005 Oct 4; 2015_121_b2_96; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Debra Satz, The moral costs of free markets, 2011 Jan 2; 2015_121_b2_97; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Jan a Mohr Lone, Philosophy for children, 2010 Dec 19; 2015_121_b2_98; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Steven Pinker, The power of thought, 2010 Dec 12; 2015_121_b2_99; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Jennifer Lackey, Disagreement, 2010 Dec 5; 2015_121_b2_100; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Joshua Landy, Reading, narrative and the self, 2010 Nov 28; 2015_121_b2_101; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Bill Uzgallis, John Locke, 2011 Feb 27; 2015_121_b2_102; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - The 2011 Dionysus awards, 2011 Feb 13; 2015_121_b2_103; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Timothy Pychyl, Procrastination, 2011 Jan 30; 2015_121_b2_104; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Joshua Kates, Derrida and Dec onstruction, 2011 Jan 16; 2015_121_b2_105; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Cynthia Gorney, Abortion, 2011 Jan 9; 2015_121_b2_106; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Frederic Stout, Cities, gentrification, and inequality, 2011 May 8; 2015_121_b2_107; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Tamara Metz, Should marriage be abolished?, 2011 May 1; 2015_121_b2_108; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - George Lakoff, The extended mind, 2011 Apr 17; 2015_121_b2_109; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Ethan Watters, What is an adult?, 2011 Apr 10; 2015_121_b2_110; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Paul Boghossian, Is it all relative?, 2011 Mar20; 2015_121_b2_111; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Simon Baron-Cohen, The psychology of evil, 2011 Jul 17; 2015_121_b2_112; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Louise Antony, Atheism and the well-lived life, 2011 Jul 10; 2015_121_b2_113; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Lera Boroditsky, Whodunit: the language of responsibility, 2011 Jun 12; 2015_121_b2_114; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Gilbert Herdt, Gay pride and prejudice, 2011 Jun 5; 2015_121_b2_115; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - John McMurthe, Irv Yalom, Helen Fisher, Geoff Nunberg, Summer reading list, 2011 May 29; 2015_121_b2_116; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Rowland Smith, Philosophy and everyday life, 2011 Jul 31; 2015_121_b2_117; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Margaret Battin, Dignity and the end of life, 2005 Sep 13; 2015_121_b2_118; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Jonathan Wolf, Marx, 2005 Sep 6; 2015_121_b2_119; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Susan Wolf, Saints and heroes, 2005 Aug 30; 2015_121_b2_120; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Jul ia Driver, Virtue, 2005 Aug 23; 2015_121_b2_121; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Anita Silvers, Disability, 2005 Aug 16; 2015_121_b2_122; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Larry Goulder, Global injustice and the environment, 2005 Aug 9; 2015_121_b2_123; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Ronald Rubin, Descartes, 2005 Aug 2; 2015_121_b2_124; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Martha Nussbaum, The indispensable emotions, 2005 Jul 26; 2015_121_b2_125; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Dave Albert, Time, 2005 Jul 12; 2015_121_b2_126; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Helen Longino, Truth and relativism, 2005 Jul 5; 2015_121_b2_127; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Robert Scharf, Zen, 2005 Jun 28; 2015_121_b2_128; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Peter Singer, Global poverty and international aid, 2005 Jun 21; 2015_121_b2_129; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Norman Daniels, Intergenerational obligations, 2005 Jun 7; 2015_121_b2_130; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Robert Solomon, Happiness, 2005 May 31; 2015_121_b2_131; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Leda Cosmides, Evolution of mind, 2005 May 24; 2015_121_b2_132; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Paul Kjellberg, Confucius, 2005 May 10; 2015_121_b2_133; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Debra Satz, Prostitution, 2005 May 10; 2015_121_b2_134; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Charles Griswold, Forgiveness, 2005 Mar 29; 2015_121_b2_135; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Sam Barondes, Neurocosmetology, 2005 Mar 22; 2015_121_b2_136; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Alexander Nehamas, Beauty, 2005 Mar 15; 2015_121_b2_137; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Anne AshbAug h, The erotic v. the pornographic, 2005 Feb 15; 2015_121_b2_138; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - John Perry Ken Taylor, Pilot #2: Terrorism, undated; 2015_121_b2_139; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - John Perry Ken Taylor, Pilot #1: Can machines think?, circa 2002; 2015_121_b2_140; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)
  - Hans Ulrich Gumbrecht, The state of public philosophy, 2011 Aug 7; 2015_121_b2_141; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 2)